Alexander N. Charters Papers
Alexander N. Charters Papers
- Media
  - [Recollections 7], charters_044; Tape is untitled. Note rubber-banded around this tape and charters_043 reads, "Tape 7 Navy Cont in NY". May be a duplicate of charters_043.; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [Recollections?], charters_025; Tape is untitled. Note enclosed with tape reads "ANC Recollections 2 sides".; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [Recollections?], charters_024; Tape is untitled. Note enclosed with tape reads "ANC [illegible] recollections Jun-July 01"; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - REGIONAL LEARNING SERVICE (11:00) repeated 5x, charters_003; no other information other than the title given above. Presumably same as charters_004 and charters_007.; VHS (Box 278)
  - Regional Learning Service Dup. [copy 1], charters_004; no other information other than the title given above. Presumably same as charters_003 and charters_007.; VHS (Box 278)
  - Regional Learning Service Dup. [copy 2], charters_007; no other information other than the title given above. Presumably same as charters_003 and charters_004.; VHS (Box 278)
  - Remembering Those Who Have Made a Difference in United States Military Voluntary Education, charters_058; co-sponsored by the American Association of State Colleges and Universities, and the American Association of Community Colleges; CD (Box 279)
  - Robert Hoghielm’s Impressions of AE collection (Robert Hoghielm - Discussion re AE collections), charters_017; Robert Höghielm was a Swedish researcher and scholar in the area of participatory education.; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - Tape 1, charters_015; unknown; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - Tape 2, charters_016; unknown; may or may not be same as charters_028; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - Tape 2, charters_028; unknown; may or may not be same as charters_016; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - What Is Europe? Presented by Dr. Kevin Wilson, charters_073; Lecture and discussion. Commercial tape produced by the BBC for The Open University, 2 sides. BBC catalog numbers printed on cassette: AC1734, AD280.; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [no title], charters_012; unknown; may be blank; VHS (Box 278)
  - [no title], charters_014; unknown; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [no title], charters_029; unknown; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [no title], charters_030; unknown; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [no title], charters_047; Tape is untitled. Note enclosed with tape reads, "At Chilliwack Re: High School Reunion at time of demolition"; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [no title], charters_048; unknown; may be blank; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Oversize 7)
  - [no title], charters_071; unknown; Dictabelt* (Box 278)
  - [no title], charters_072; unknown; Dictabelt* (Box 278)